[
    {
        "question": "Game question: What year was among us made? (Medium)",
        "answers": ["2018"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Security question: What is a thing that you should NERVER share with anybody at all time about your account as of 2022? [Say the one you think it is: password, email, 2fa, token] (Medium)",
        "answers": ["mainly token but as well password and email/2fa"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Security question: Which one is more safe? http or https (Medium)",
        "answers": ["https"]
    },
    {
        "question": "it is needed to go to school to get money in the future? (Medium)",
        "answers": [
            "in reality, you actually dont have to go to school to get moneny in the future, the only most important part of school for most people is just the simple math (+, ×, ÷, -),  you can do homeschooling and more, Learning what you want to do in the future is the best, such as programming, being a good content creator (this counts being a youtuber and more), for youtube, you gonna have to make good quality videos and Youtube shorts and as well livestreams, for anything on youtube or a video website excluding livestreaming, it is highly highly recommended to use a great video editer, a nice video editer i use is DaVinci Resolve Free version, its a good idea to make videos on a computer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Web question: In a website browser address bar, what does “www” stand for? (Medium)",
        "answers": ["World Wide Web"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Food question: What is sushi traditionally wrapped in? (Kinda Easy)",
        "answers": ["Edible seaweed"]
    },
    {
        "question": "IRL question: In which European city would you find Orly airport? (Might be Hard)",
        "answers": ["Paris"]
    },
    {
        "question": "IRL question: What color eyes do most humans have as of 2022? (Kinda easy)",
        "answers": ["Brown"]
    },
    {
        "question": "IRL question: What is the lowest army rank of a US soldier? (Maybe hard)",
        "answers": ["Private"]
    },
    {
        "question": "IRL question: How many hearts does an octopus have? (Might be a bit hard)",
        "answers": ["3"]
    },
    {
        "question": "IRL question: How many eyes does a bee have? (Might be hard)",
        "answers": ["5"]
    },
    {
        "question": "IRL question: Which country was the Caesar salad invented in? (Might be hard)",
        "answers": ["Mexico"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Online question: What is the Twitter bird’s official name? (Kinda easy)",
        "answers": ["Larry"]
    },
    {
        "question": "IRL question: What is a community of ants called? (Medium)",
        "answers": ["A colony"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Special question: What does it mean for somebody to be a furry? (Easy/Medium)",
        "answers": [
            "it normally means that the person is interested in Anthropomorphic animals (human like animals), Thats literally it, no joke"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Carrots are a good source of which vitamin? (Should be easy)",
        "answers": ["Vitamin A"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What has a gravitational pull so strong that even light cannot escape it? (Should be a bit easy)",
        "answers": ["Black Hole"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Normal question: How many letters are there in the english alphabet? (Medium)",
        "answers": ["26!"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Game question: What year was Classic: Crossroads made by Roblox? (Medium)",
        "answers": ["2007"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dev question: Who is the creator of this bot? (A bit easy)",
        "answers": ["adudu21", "Hecker", "Hecker#1844"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dev question: What year was this bot made? (Medium)",
        "answers": ["2022"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Game question: What year was Friday Night Funkin made? (Medium)",
        "answers": ["2020"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Youtube question: What year was the channel of MrBeast Made? (Medium)",
        "answers": ["2012"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Game question: Who made FE2/Flood escape 2 on roblox? (Medium)",
        "answers": ["Crazyblox"]
    },

    {
        "question": "Normal question: Are cats bigger than humans normaly? (Normal)",
        "answers": ["no!"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Youtube question: Does mrbeast have over 2+ channels? (Normal)",
        "answers": ["yes"]
    },
    {
        "question": "internet question: Does google collect data? (Easy)",
        "answers": ["yes"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Game question: On roblox are you able to see your moderation history?",
        "answers": ["yes"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Normal question: Are dogs bigger than humans normaly?",
        "answers": ["no!"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Game question: What is the name of the first ever roblox group? (Medium)",
        "answers": ["RobloHunks"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Game question: Who is the CEO of roblox in 2022? (Medium)",
        "answers": ["David Baszucki"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Game question: Was there a beta version of roblox, if so then what was the name? (Medium)",
        "answers": ["DynaBlocks"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Discord question: What was the most popular server on discord in 2022? (Medium)",
        "answers": ["mid journey"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Math question: What is 2039x3x0? (Easy)",
        "answers": ["0"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Math question: What is 5x5? (Easy)",
        "answers": ["25!"]
    }
]
